Chase Going Woodhouse Papers 1983.0009
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series IV: Status of Women, undated, 1908-1981
  - Subseries A: Organizations and Publications, undated, 1923-1981
    - National Women's Party, 1930-1945
    - National Women's Political Caucus (NWPC), 1972-1977
    - Newsletter, Center for Continuing Education of Women, 1973-1979
    - News Letter of the Standing Conference of Women's Organizations Series 37-39, 1967
    - Oregon report on Black Working Women with Dependents, undated [c. 1967]
    - Permanent Commission on the Status of Women (PCSW), 1974-1979
    - Phi Delta Gamma, 1966-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Pi Lambda Theta/Phi Upsilon Omicron, 1936/1929
    - The Planner, 1970
    - Political Participation Program v. 1-8, 1959
    - President's Commission on the Status of Women, 1963 (Box 34:, Folder 4 fl)
    - Primetime, 1975 (Box 35)
    - Public Affairs pamphlets, 1938-1974
    - Regionalization of Community Nursing and Health Services Coordinators, Reports, 1972
    - Republican National Committee, 1949, 1953
    - Sister, 1974-1975
    - Spokeswoman, 1970-1978 (Box 35:, Folder 2 fl)
    - State Governments, 1961-1975 (Box 35:, Folder 18 fl)
    - State Governments, 1930-1975 (Box 36:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Tapestry, 1980
    - Title VII Report, 1970
    - United Nations, 1955-1980
    - US Government: Congress, Senate and federal agencies, 1930-1971
    - United States Assembly of Commission on the Status of Women, 1969
    - US Center for International Women's Year, 1975 (Box 36:, Folder 2 fl)
    - US Government, 1975
    - Vital Issues, 1975
    - Wartime Training Programs of Women's Military Service, 1946
    - Washington Newsletter for Women, 1970
    - Washington Spectator, 1980
    - Western Political Quarterly, 1980
    - Woman, The Majority Report, undated
    - Women Activist, 1970-1971
    - Women's Campaign Fund, Inc., 1979-1980
    - Women's Centennial Congress, 1940
    - Women's Equity Action League (WEAL), 1971-1975 (Box 36:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Women's Foundation, 1945
    - Women's International Religious Fellowship, 1977
    - Women in Action, 1971-1973
    - Women in the World, 1973-1976
    - Women in War on Poverty, 1967, 1969
    - Women Lawyers Journal, 1947
    - Women's New York, 1975-1980
    - Women's Organization, 1944-1979
    - Woman's Place, Inc., 1967, 1975
    - Women Speaking, 1961
    - Women Today, 1972-1980
    - Women Today, 1972-1980
    - Women's Unit, 1967-1974
    - Women United, 1971
    - Women's Voice, 1972
    - Women and work, 1973-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 3 fl)
  - Subseries B: Topics, undated, 1908-1981
    - Against the ERA, 1938-1947 (Box 37)
    - Bibliography, 1966-1970
    - Black Women, 1970-1971
    - Child and family care, 1975, 1979
    - Connecticut history, 1968, 1976
    - Declaration of understanding between men and women, undated
    - Different states, 1929
    - Discrimination against women, 1970 (Box 37:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Economics, 1928-1980
    - Educated women in America, ca. 1930
    - Education, 1908-1981 (Box 37:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Employment, 1922-1981 (Box 37:, Folder 3 fl)
    - Equal pay and rights in the workplace, 1964-1971
    - Equal rights, ca. 1940-1945
    - ERA and women's rights, 1971, 1973
    - Family, 1927-1973
    - History of Women in America, 1964-1976 (Box 38:, Folder 2 fl)
    - Institutes, 1960-1975
    - Lectures and workshops, 1951-1975
    - Legislation, 1969-1979
    - Marriage and family, life for women with jobs, 1919-1979 (Box 38:, Folder 3 fl)
    - National organizations involved with consumer interests, 1966
    - Occupational opportunities, 1925-1978 (Box 38:, Folder 3 fl)
    - Political activities, 1973
    - Pro-ERA, 1926-1975
    - Sex discrimination, 1969-1980
    - Social sciences, 1933-1980
    - War and peace, 1967-1981
    - Women, men and the doctorate, 1974
    - Women in other countries, 1949-1973 (Box 39:, Folder 3 fl)
    - Women in politics, 1934-1975
    - Women in War, 1942-1944 (Box 39:, Folder 3 fl)
    - Women in the work force, 1933-1980 (Box 39:, Folder 3 fl)
    - Women's organization information, undated
    - Woodhouse Biography, undated
    - General information, 1909-1977
    - Unidentified, 1921-1981 (Box 39:, Folder 2 fl)
- Series V: Constitutional Convention [Resolutions committee], 1965, 1969
  - Letter to Governor Dempsey, 1969 (Box 40)
  - Public meetings: Norwalk, Meriden, Torrington, Norwich (Box 40:, Folder 2 fl)
  - Committee on Resolutions: public hearings
  - Convention seminar
  - Voting rights
  - Bill of rights
  - Correspondence
  - Constitutional resolutions, executive subcommittee meetings
  - Personnel notices
  - Rough drafts
  - Notice of meetings
  - List of subcommittees
  - Bulletins—Constitutional Convention
  - General Correspondence
  - September hearings
  - August 30 hearings
  - August 31 hearings
  - [August 26 hearings]
  - [August 24 hearings]
  - [August 23 hearings]
  - Assignments of subcommittees
  - Resolution on annual sessions
  - Correspondence
  - Resolutions
  - Resolution on amending the Constitution
  - Resolutions
  - Home Rule (Box 40:, Folder 2 fl)
  - Reappointment (Box 440:, Folder 3 fl)
  - Judiciary/executive (Box 40:, Folder 3 fl)
  - Eminent domain (Box 40:, Folder 3 fl)
  - General (Box 40:, Folder 3 fl)
  - [Resolutions]
  - [Resolutions]
  - [Resolutions—annotated]
- Series VI: Public Service, undated, 1929-1982
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission of CT, 1975 (Box 41)
  - Citizen Advisory Council on Safe Schools. CT Annual State Plan for the Administration of Vocational Education P.L. 94-482, 1982 (Box 41:, Folder 2 fl)
  - Citizen's Advisory Council on Safe Schools, Report, 1980
  - Commission on CT's Future, 1978
  - Community Council of the Capital Region, 1976
  - Comprehensive Health Planning, Expectations Study Group, 1971-1972
  - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1975-1981
  - Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, 1968
  - Consumer Committee, State Defense Council, 1942
  - Consumer Interests organizations, 1966
  - Correspondence: ERA and Request for publications, 1929-1947 (Box 41:, Folder 3 fl)
  - Correspondence: Congressional, 1949
  - Criminal Justice Commission, undated
  - Democratic Party, 1970, 1973
  - Governor's Committee on Environmental Policy, Report of Housing Function Panel, 1970
  - National Roster of Scientific and Specialized Personnel, 1942-1943
  - New England Energy Task Force, 1977
  - Office of Defense Mobilization, 1951
  - Senate Bill 357, 1977
  - Southeast Connecticut Planning Agency, 1972
  - Planning and Zoning Board, Sprague, CT, 1965-1980 (Box 41:, Folder 2 fl)
  - State Defense Council Women's Division, 1942
  - Task Force on Education, 1965-1967
  - War Manpower Commission, 1943
  - Scrapbook of clippings, 1950-1952
  - Structural Organization of the State and Local Government Of Connecticut, 1939
  - History of the War Manpower Commission in CT, 1945 (Box 41:, Folder 2 fl)
- Series VII: Juvenile Justice, undated, 1951-1980
  - Connecticut Justice Commission—grants, 1978-1980 (Box 42)
  - Definitions—legal terms, undated
  - Juvenile treatment programs, ca. 1978
  - Project Juvenile Justice, 1974-1979
  - Review of the 1979 CT General Assembly bills impacting the criminal, undated
  - Subseries A: Meetings, workshops and symposia, 1974-1978
    - Juvenile justice system
      - Danielson area meeting, 1975
      - Hartford area meeting, 1975 (Box 42:, Folder 2 fl)
      - New Haven area meeting, 1974
      - New London area meeting, 1974
      - Norwalk area meeting, 1974
    - Child in Trouble, 1976-1977
    - Juvenile Justice systems: Legal Rights of Children, 1974
    - Law related curriculum, 1978
    - Serious juvenile offender, 1978
    - Troubled youth, 1976
  - Subseries B: Publications, undated, 1951-1980
    - Bibliographies and reviews, undated
    - Auerbach Service Bureau, undated (Box 43)
      - Laws relating to child, parent and state, 1979
      - Legal rights of children, [1975?]
      - Legal rights of children, children, the family and the State under CT law, 1977
      - Legal rights of children update, 1979
      - Outline of CT statutes and administrative regulations, 1976
      - Police programs in schools, 1977
      - Role of humanities in reconsideration of the Juvenile justice..., undated
      - School law, 1978
    - Change—a juvenile justice quarterly, 1978
    - CT Citizen's Advisory Council on Safe Schools, undated
    - CT Justice Commission, undated
    - CT Municipalities-based youth services, 1976
    - CT State Board of Education, 1979
    - CT State Department of Education, 1979
    - CT/State of, 1978
    - Constitutional Rights Foundation, 1976
    - Decision-making, 1977
    - Delinquency in education, 1979
    - Discipline through affection, 1951
    - Effect of legal sanctions on juvenile delinquency, 1977
    - Girls in the juvenile justice system: sex discrimination or Distinction?, 1976
    - Guide to law-related education, [1976]
    - In search of justice: legal education, 1978
    - Job opportunities for youth, undated
    - Justice in the school system, 1976, 1978
    - Just-us, 1978
    - Juvenile Justice system: what happens?, 1975
    - Law-related education, 1975, 1978
    - Legislation, undated
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1974
    - National Council on Juvenile Court Judges, 1975
    - National Juvenile justice program collaboration, [1978]
    - National network of youth advisory boards, 1977
    - Police Youth Offender's resource guide, undated
    - Policeman's criminal law observer, 1976 (Box 44)
    - Quality of life for Connecticut children, [1974]
    - Recommendations to the state Board of Education, undated
    - Services for youth: a CT directory, 1975
    - States are funding juvenile justice projects..., 1980
    - Synergy, 1979
    - Youth and law demonstration, 1978
    - US Department of Justice, 1976
    - West Publishing Co., 1975
    - Law in action series, undated
- Series VIII: Recognitions, 1913-1981
  - CT State Federation of the AAUW, 1936-1941 (Box OS)
  - National Council of Negro Women, Inc., 1948 (Box 45)
  - Connecticut Vocational Association, 1960, 1967
  - Women's Community Organization Month, 1966
  - ALTRUSA International, 1967
  - Connecticut Valley Council of B'Nai B'rith Women, 1968-1969
  - Cooperative Extension Service, 1969
  - Department of State, 1972, 1974
  - United State Committee for UNICEF, 1973-1974
  - Southeastern Connecticut Regional Planning Agency, [1973]
  - National Council for Community Services to International Visitors, 1975
  - New London County Bar Association, 1978
  - Volunteer Action Center, 1979
  - Connecticut Magazine, 1981
  - American Legion Auxiliary, undated
  - Connecticut Humanities Council, undated
  - New England Solar Energy Research Institute, undated
  - Mohegan Community College—C.G. Woodhouse Poetry Prize, 1975
  - U.S. Treasury Department, 1943 (Box 46)
  - New England Association of County Agricultural Agents, 1969
  - New England 4-H Club Agent Association, 1969
  - New England Association of Extension Home Economics, 1969
  - Ladies Auxiliary to the Veterans of Foreign Wars of the United States, 1974
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1974
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission of CT, undated
  - Connecticut Consortium for Law-Related Education, undated
  - McGill University, 1913
  - University of Connecticut, 1980
  - Advisory Council on Community Affairs, 1961
  - Commission to Study the Establishment of a Branch of the University of Connecticut to serve southeastern Connecticut, 1961
  - Advisory Council for the Unemployment Compensation Act, 1962-1967
  - Advisory Council on Community Affairs, 1967
  - Commission on Housing within an Optimum Living Environment and new Planned Communities, 1969
  - Commission on Connecticut's Future, 1976-1979
  - Press releases and invitations, 1952-1976 (Box 5 fl)
  - Reelection poster, undated (Box OS)
  - Photographs, undated, ca. 1920s-1970 (Box 46)
    - Woodhouse, Chase Going (5), 1920s-1970
    - COSERV Board of Directors, 1965
- Series IX: Ephemera, undated, 1943-1945
  - War Ration Books, undated (Box 47)
  - Supplemental Mileage Ration, 1944 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_e6f71d9ccd15b56080f0de157b4891fd)
  - U.S. Naval Air Transport Service Priority Certificate, 1945
  - United States Employment Service Card, 1943
  - Travel Expense Diary, 1913-1917